# **RAY PERRY**

# Summary

Hard-working, adaptable, generalist with over nine years of experience in full-stack web development. Self-starter; works well in a team environment and approaches problems with a "can-do" attitude. Prioritizes effectively and works under deadlines with ease. Has lead multiple teams in high-pressure situations. Understands what needs to be done and acts accordingly, learning additional roles when required. Offers a fresh perspective to situations and is not afraid to ask questions.

### Technical Skills

PROFICIENCIES: JavaScript, Lisp, Scheme

PLATFORMS: Node.js

FRAMEWORKS: Angular, Vue.js

DATASTORES: MongoDB, MySQL, Redis

# Work Experience (Full-time)

#### **ThoughtWorks** | Senior Consultant | December 2019 – present

Worked with a large fast-service restaurant chain to augment and integrate payment terminals with previous-generation transaction gateway and vendor APIs.

## Oranj | Full Stack Engineer | December 2017 - December 2019

Worked on a suite of advisor, investor, and analytics applications, focused on account aggregation and rebalancing. Built a meta-object browser to facilitate the association of entities across multiple systems.

#### PMMI Media Group | Sr. Web Developer | August 2017 – November 2017

Worked on a data aggregation tool that consumed data from IBM Silverpop, Salesforce, and a Redis cache.

# QuikOrder, Inc. | JavaScript Engineer | February 2016 – July 2016

Maintained and augmented multi-purpose food order system. Integrated multiple third-party APIs. Added smart localization that adhered to WCAG, I18n, and a11y standards. Created various middleware for our Node.js-based system.

#### RDI/A Digital | Web Developer | March 2014 - March 2015

Deployed multiple to-spec sites for Publicis Health Media, PAC12, The NFL Network, Delta Faucets.

## Work Experience (Contract)

STA Group | March 2017 - June 2017 | Data Visualization Dashboard

STA Group | November 2016 - March 2017 | Data Visualization Dashboard

Blitsy | September 2016 - November 2016 | Main Platform

Cars.com | December 2015 - February 2016 | Core Team

HERE | August 2015 - October 2015 | Maps Team

IndyBuild | March 2015 - June 2015 | Main Platform

New Home Star | December 2013 - March 2014 | Main Platform

Freelance Work (B2C), various clients | August 2010 - October 2013 | Brochure sites

#### Education/Certifications

Western Governors University – Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science (2019 - 2020) CompTIA Project+ (June 2019)